[Music]
the moment life takes a beautiful
turn your life becomes all about
them their smile becomes your
happiness their needs become your
priority their dreams become your
aspirations but from their first step to
their dreams they chase protect your
loved ones from an unpredictable future
with a long-term Financial
[Music]
Protection presenting ICICI Pro I
protect Smart Life continuity option a
term insurance with flexibility to
receive life cover as monthly income for
up to 30 years you may choose income
option where your family gets monthly
income for 10 20 or 30 years lumpsum
plus income option where your family
gets a lumpsum some plus monthly income
for 10 20 or 30 years let's understand
the lumsum plus income option let's say
Mr Gupta is a 35-year-old salaried
family man with a daughter in case of an
unfortunate event Mr Gupta wants his
loved ones to receive a one-time lum sum
of 50 lakh rupees and 25,000 rupees as
monthly income for a period of 30 years
then Mr Gupta needs to pay 19,00
965 rupees per anom for 40 years so that
his nominee can receive a lumpsum of 50
lakh rupes and a monthly income of
25,000 for 30 years in his absence
similarly at an annual premium of
18769 rupees perom his nominee can get a
lumpsum of 5050 lakh rupees and a
monthly income of 25,000 rupees for 20
years and for an annual premium of 16,6
20117 perom his nominee can get a lump
suum of 50 lakh rupees and a monthly
income of 25,000 rupees for 10 years
ICICI Pro I protect Smart Life
continuity option a plan that protects
your loved ones from the uncertainties
of life for long term because your
responsibilities extend beyond your
[Music]
lifetime